Hi, I'm Hannah. We're here at Leighton Stone Blueprint.
So one of the things that I love most about coming here is that it's a small group,
and so you always feel like you've got someone's attention that are focusing on that technique
and you're going to injure yourself, but it's also really great. It's a real community.
I really love that sense that actually I can be kind of supported to be as I can be.
The instructors all really kind of hone in on you. They really understand what your limits are
and how far they can push you, and they do really push you and they really challenge you,
and then they'll come over and say, hang on a sec, what do you put it on there,
and hand you a different way that you think just that I forgot it in me today, but you always do,
and so they always manage to kind of understand exactly what you are capable of
before you understand it, which is brilliant.